[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet has an apparent magnitude of  -2.8 to -1.6?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Venus", "Mercury", "Mars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does the gestation period of elephants last?", "correct_answer": "22 months", "incorrect_answers": ["30 months", "18 months", "12 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is the most common natural pollinator of the pineapple plant?", "correct_answer": "Hummingbird", "incorrect_answers": ["Gall wasp", "Bumblebee", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following best defines the octopus related word midden?", "correct_answer": "a pile of shells", "incorrect_answers": ["a burrow in the sand used as a den", "a hole in the rock face or corral used as a den", "a chemical in the ink sprayed from an octopus siphon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which wall is used for computer protection in the Internet or other networks?", "correct_answer": "Firewall", "incorrect_answers": ["Wooden wall", "Brickwall", "Protective wall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Platypuses are venomous.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the European peninsula on which Italy is located?", "correct_answer": "Italian Peninsula", "incorrect_answers": ["Scandinavian Peninsula", "Iberian Peninsula", "Balkan Peninsula"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of his own body does Hannibal Lecter cut off in the 2001 thriller movie Hannibal?", "correct_answer": "Hand", "incorrect_answers": ["Ear", "Finger", "Toe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1968 song, recorded by the Beatles, was written by Paul McCartney, who wanted to cheer up Lennons son, Julian.", "correct_answer": "Hey Jude", "incorrect_answers": ["Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds", "While My Guitar Gently Weeps", "Happy Birthday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This huge company is often referred to as Big Blue.", "correct_answer": "IBM", "incorrect_answers": ["Hewlett-Packard", "Microsoft", "Cisco Systems, Inc."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these studies are chinchillas used as animal models?", "correct_answer": "Studies of the auditory system", "incorrect_answers": ["Studies of vocalization", "Eyesight studies", "Studies of the reproductive system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most populous island in the world?", "correct_answer": "Java", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuba", "Borneo", "Honshu"]}]